[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This complex is a phase in child development characterized by jealousy and rivalry with the same sex parent.", "correct_answer": "Oedipal complex", "incorrect_answers": ["Messianic complex", "Electra complex", "Castration complex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed Episode V:  The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": "Irvin Kershner", "incorrect_answers": ["None of the above", "George Lucas", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Matryoshka is a wooden nested doll, whose name is derived from the female first name Matryona, which was popular among peasants in this country.", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Poland", "Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This formation is a conical hill or mountain. It is formed by mantle material being pressed through an opening in the Earths crust.", "correct_answer": "A volcano", "incorrect_answers": ["A hill", "An earthquake", "A geyser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Cocktail, Jordans family was extremely wealthy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alfred Hitchcock directed the 1941 movie Mr. and Mrs. Smith.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the other name of Doc Hudson, an ex-racecar in the movie Cars?", "correct_answer": "The Hudson Hornet", "incorrect_answers": ["Guido", "The Horton Hornet", "Lightning McQueen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sings As Time Goes By, the first song in the Sleepless in Seattle soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Durante", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Connick, Jr.", "Joe Cocker", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the official languages spoken in Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Malagasy, French and English", "incorrect_answers": ["Malagasy and English", "Malagasy and French", "English and French"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for a layer of gasses that surround a large object and are held in place by the objects gravity?", "correct_answer": "Atmosphere", "incorrect_answers": ["Molecular mass", "Escape velocity", "Surface gravity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal character is Don Lino, voiced by Robert De Niro in the 2004 comedy movie Shark Tale?", "correct_answer": "Shark", "incorrect_answers": ["Octopus", "Manta ray", "Blue whale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie The Last Dragon, Leroy catches a 9mm. bullet in his mouth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]